(Sheldon:)Would you like to talk about it?
(Leonard:)Penny proposed,
and I didn't say yes.
(Sheldon:)-Why not?
-That's a good question.
(Sheldon:)Does that mean the
relationship is over?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Why don't you ask her?
(Leonard:)Because I'm afraid
to know the answer.
Wel... I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)That's it? You're not
gonna make some dumb joke
(Leonard:)or some inappropriate comment?
(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)You're my friend, and... I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)Did you just put
a "kick me" sign on my back?
(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)That wouldn't be funny at all.
Star Wars audition, take ons.
(Howard:)Starring Howard Joel Wolowitz,
real-life astronaut.
(Howard:)Vader is here,
(Howard:)now, on this moon.
(Howard:)I felt his presence.
(Howard:)He's come for me.
He can feel when I'm near--
(Bernadette:)How many times
do I have to tell you
(Bernadette:)to replace the toilet paper
when it's empty?!
-I'm in the middle of something!
-So am I!